

# Phelisa Nonzwakazi Gqwetha



+27740192226



phelisaggwetha@gmail.com



Cape Town, Western Cape

#### Linked in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/phel isa-nonzwakazi-gqwetha-64b17 31bb/

## EDUCATION

#### Matric

Matthew Goniwe Memorial High School 2014-2018

# CERTIFICATE

**AWS Cloud Practitioner** 

Full Stack Agile Development

## References

Mr Makhosandile, Project

codeX - Mentor 067 156 8798,

makhosandile@projectcodex.co

### PROFILE

As an AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner and the experience gained with working on industry specific Information Technology (I.T) Projects I enjoy challenging myself with new technologies and I'm willing to learn, explore more in the IT industry because I believe that is my passion.

## SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, React.JS, Node.JS, SQL
- Git and GitHub,
- TDD using mocha
- Running tests on Travis
- Linux and Windows
- Figma for designing
- Troubleshooting
- AWS
- Team Player and Time Management

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **IT Tech Support**

Praesignis | Cape Town | 06/01/2022 - 23/12/2022

This was a one year program Learnership which was focusing on IT and AWS certification.

- Focus on Troubleshooting, problem solving and more
- Creating websites for projects
- AWS certification with practical labs

#### **Software Developer Intern**

Project codeX | Cape Town | 16/01/2020 - 23/12/2021

- Focus on the Front-end and Back-end.
- Build a functioning and fully documented application.

Desiree Hare, Praesignis—
Facilitator/Manager

063 703 7380,

desiree.hare@praesignis.com

• Following Scrum practices to develop the app in a team of 4.

## PROJECTS

#### 2022: Black-Jack-Game

https://comforting-pony-6ed839.netlify.app

GitHub Repository: https://github.com/phelisa2020/Black-Jack-Game Black Jack is a Blackjack is a casino banking game. It is the most widely played casino banking game in the world, it uses decks of 52 cards and descends from a global family of casino banking games known as Twenty-One. I build it using javascipt.

#### **2021: BUDGET APP -**

https://budget-app-2.herokuapp.com/

GitHub Repository: https://github.com/phelisa2020/hacktor Budget app allows you to make a monthly budget to save money. By putting all your monthly expenses then it will tell you the money that is left. Our focus was on the students who spend their money carelessly. This app was built using ExpressJS, NodeJS. It was deployed on GitHub and Heroku, using Git and GitHub. This was a team project for the Hackathon.